Exercise 1-28. Reading with Staircase Intonation. Read the following with clear
intonation where marked. Hello. My name is Anne. I'm taking American accent training.
There's a lot to learn, but I hope to make it as enjoyable as possible. I should pick
up on The American intonation pattern pretty easily, although the only way to
get it is to practice all the time.
I use the up and down or peaks and valleys intonation more than I used to. I've been
paying attention to pitch, too. It's like walking down a staircase.
I've been talking to a lot of Americans lately, and they tell me that I'm easier
to understand.
Anyway, I could go on and on, but the important thing is to listen well and
sound good. Well, what do you think? Do I?